Henry Liu

4153 Hammonds FRY Evans, GA 30809 (704) 267-3376 Henryyin12@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Enthusiastic full-stack web developer with recently learned skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, node.js, and React. Earned a certificate in full stack web development from Georgia Tech boot camp and close to three years of credit in Accounting from the University of Georgia. Completed a project in a team of four on an application allowing the user to search for a keyword and comparing the news landscape before and during the COVID-19 pandemic.

EDUCATION

University of Georgia, Athens, GA

AUG 2016 - MAR 2020

Lakeside High School, Evans, GA

AUG 2012 - MAY 2016

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Orbic Eye Care, Martinez, GA — Receptionist

JUN 2017 - AUG 2017

Schedule appointments and receive customers, check for customer insurance eligibility, provide information about appointment availability and products, copy and file paper documents and records, operate the cash register to receive payments, and answer telephone calls

University of Georgia Office of Student Financial Aid, Athens, GA — *Peer Financial Aid Counselor*

AUG 2016 - JAN 2017

Complete basic training in federal student aid administration and answer emails from students related to financial aid

CLASSES

Financial Accounting

Managerial Accounting

Risk Management and Insurance

Introduction to Information Systems

Microeconomics

Macroeconomics

Personal Finance

Business Statistics

SKILLS

Front-End Web Development

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft PowerPoint

Microsoft Word